Guide to the Pierre Hohenberg, Deputy Provost for Science and Technology, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Pierre Hohenberg, Deputy provost for science and technology, Yale University, records
1980-2003
RU 995
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
23.75
The records consist of topical files maintained by Pierre Hohenberg and records of the Office of Deputy Provost for Science and Technology at Yale.
Yale University. Office of the Provost
Hohenberg, Pierre
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 3-B (YRG 3-B), Records of Yale deputy, associate, and assistant provosts.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Office of the Deputy Provost, 2005-2008.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of topical files maintained by Pierre Hohenberg and records of the Office of Deputy Provost for Science and Technology at Yale.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Office of the Provost
- General and departmental files, circa 1987-2000; Accession 2006-A-124
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2035
  - A-21, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Affirmative Action, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Andes, 1996 October 21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Animal Care, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Animal Facilities
    - YACUC, 1998 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - YARC, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AURA, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AYA, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - BBS, 1996 April 8 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Biomedical Engineering
    - 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Graduate, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Budget
    - FY 2002, 1993-1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Operating and Capital Budgets, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 13 - 14)
    - MBB pres. to Provost/Med Dean, 1999 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - FAS Budget, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Canal, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Capital Budget, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Capital Spending, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Carnegie Mellon, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Centers
    - "C"enters vs "c"enters, 1987 January 12 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Child Study Ct, 1997 June 8 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - IBM/ Yale Neural, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Mass Spectrometry, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - CESOF, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - COI
    - 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Committee, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - History, 1989-1999 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - CCR
    - 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Cooperative Research
    - Bickerton, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Copyright, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Licensing, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Patent Other (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - OCR, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Royalty Sharing, 1993-1999 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Technology Transfer, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - COS, 1998 June 22 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - CTAN (aka NNC)
    - 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - CTAN Agreement, 1990-1997 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - DSSG, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Department Long Range Plans, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 50 - 51)
  - Diversity, 1999 February 23 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Dual Careers, 1998 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Educational Alliance, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Endowment
    - Chemistry, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Engineering, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Profesorships, 1997 April 7 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Engineering
    - Bromley/V. Bush Award, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Design, 1998 November 2 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Graduate Fellowships, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - NEC Corporation, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Long-Range Planning/Space, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Environment Miscellaneous, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 67 - 68)
  - Environ Sci Fac (ESF)
    - Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Design-Planning, 1994-1998 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Design-Team Meeting, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Faculty Affairs
    - Faculty Orientation, 1989 October 6 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - FAS: Dual Career, 1999 October 12 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Faculty Slots, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - FAS Appointment, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Gifts vs. Grants, 1996 November 1 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Grants and Contracts, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Hartigan Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Haskins Lab
    - 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Liaison Committee, 1988-1994 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Haskins Misc., 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Hellman Family Fellowships
    - History, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - HHMI (Box 3)
    - Misc., 1999 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Policies, 1990 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Horizon, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Human Resources, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Insurance, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - ITS
    - Committees, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Policies, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 98 - 100)
    - Reports, 1996 May 22 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Science Depts, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Leaves of Absence, 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Math Slots, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Moving Expenses, 1998 August 3 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Nat Bureau Econ Res, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Nobel Laureates, 1999 October 15 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Patents/Students, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Peabody Museum
    - General, 1998 February 11 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Budget, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - ESF Collaboration Move, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Peking Yale Center, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Postdocs
    - 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Office, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 114 - 115)
  - Prizes and Awards
    - General, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Japan Prize, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Robert A. Welch Award in Chemistry, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Professional Schools, 1999 November 23 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Project X, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Proposals
    - Dryfus, 1975-1996 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - General, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - NSF/MRI, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Packard Proposals, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Packard, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Whitaker, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - NSF/MRI, 2000 January 18 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Provosts/AR public letters, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Provost
    - Committees, 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Provostial Committees, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Hohenberg, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Hohenberg-Research ACCT, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Sr. Admin Assoc. (Science and Tech), 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Public Affairs, 1996-1999 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Rankings, 1998 September 18 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Reaccredidation, 1999 September 1 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Recommendation Letters, 1996-1999 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Research
    - Admin/Yale, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Compliance, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Equipment Transfer, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Federal, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Indirect Costs, 1991-1997 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Issues, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Other Institutions, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Org of Research, 1996-1999 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Research Officers
    - Meeting, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - 1999 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Research Support
    - AD Hoc Com, 1988-89 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Retirement
    - 1990-1999 (Box 4, Folder 165 - 169)
  - Science Hill Misc.
    - General, 1999 February 10 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - Science Hill, 1986-1996 (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - I Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - Med School Sci Hill Presentation, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Chem Space and Resources, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Science Hill/ MISC, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Science Hill Phase II Task Force
    - Preliminary, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - 1999 (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Science Hill Planning
    - Interviews, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - Planning Study, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Planning, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Science Policy Committee, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Science and Tech Forum, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Shops, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Sponsored Research, 1995 November 21 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Studies in the Environment
    - 1999 (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Teaching/Learning Init., 1998 April 7 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Team Lux, 1997 November 12 (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Tropical Biology Association, 1997 February 20 (Box 5, Folder 196)
  - UCAR, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 197)
  - VIGRE, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - Yale-Chile, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - Yale College, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - Yale University Policies, 1980-1999 (Box 5, Folder 201)
  - Yale University Policies-Med School, 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 202)
  - YSEA, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - Anthropology Dept.
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 204)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 205)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Applied Math Program
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 207)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 208)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Applied Physics Dept.
    - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 210)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 211)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - Astronomy Dept
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 213)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 214)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 215)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 216)
    - Telescope, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 217)
    - Yale Southern Observatory, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Biomedical Engineering Dept, 1999 June 2 (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Chemical Engineering Dept
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 220)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 221)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 222)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Chemistry Dept
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - Summer, 1998 August 31 (Box 6, Folder 226)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Computer Sci Dept
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 228)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 229)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 230)
    - Unsuccessful Comp Sci, 1998 February 29 (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - EEB Dept.
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 232)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 233)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 234)
    - MCDB, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 235)
    - Planning and MCDB, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 236)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - Electrical Eng Dept
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 238)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 240)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 241)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 242)
    - Microelectronics Center, 1998 August 4 (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - NEC Fellowship, 1996 March 28 (Box 6, Folder 244)
    - New Major-Dual EE/CS, 1997 March 11 (Box 6, Folder 245)
  - FOE Dept
    - Engineering Building, 1999 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 246)
    - Long-Range Plan, 1999 February 23 (Box 6, Folder 247)
    - Professorships, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 248)
    - Dean Advertisement, 1999 October 4 (Box 6, Folder 249)
    - TA's, 1995 August 23 (Box 6, Folder 250)
    - Slots, 1999 February 23 (Box 6, Folder 251)
    - Dean Search, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 252)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 253)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 254)
    - 1987-88 (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies Dept
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 256)
    - SAC General Plan, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - G and G Dept
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 258)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 259)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 261)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 262)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 263)
    - Lecturer-Environmental Fluid, 1998 May 13 (Box 6, Folder 265)
    - Report-Planning Committee, 1995 March 13 (Box 6, Folder 266)
  - Linguistics Dept
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 267)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 268)
  - Mathematics Dept
    - Teaching, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - Gibbs, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - Math Positions, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - Math Slots, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 272)
    - Math Matrix, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 273)
    - Math Rebates, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 274)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 275)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 276)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 277)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 278)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 279)
  - MB and B Dept.
    - 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 280)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 281)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 282)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - Administration, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - Appointments and Promotions, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - Budget Agreement, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - HHMI, 1996 July 18 (Box 7, Folder 288)
    - Salary Agreement, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 289)
    - Comp, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 290)
    - 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 291)
  - MCDB Dept.
    - 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 292)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 293)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 294)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 295)
  - Mechanical Engineering Dept
    - 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 297)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 298)
    - Senior Design Course, 1996 August 19 (Box 7, Folder 299)
  - Peabody Museum
    - 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - Summer, 1999 July 22 (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 302)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 303)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 304)
  - Physics Dept.
    - 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 305)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 306)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - Teaching Labs, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 308)
  - Psychology Dept.
    - 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 311)
  - Statistics Dept.
    - 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 313)
- General and individual departmental files, 1980-2001; Accession 2006-A-178
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - Alice, 1998 November 5 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Animal Facilities
    - YARC, 2001 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - YARC, 2000 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual Reports, 7/2000-6/2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Biomedical Engineering
    - 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7 - 8)
  - Brookhaven National Lab, 2000 February 29 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Budget
    - Operating and Capital Budgets, 2000 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Capital Budget, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Departmental Budget--MBB, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Business Affairs
    - Regional Center, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Research: PI Package, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Centers
    - Astronomy and Astrophysics, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Combustion Center, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Center for Internet Studies (CIS), 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Center for International and Area Studies, 2001 April 11 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Center for Study of Globalization, 2000 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - National Foundation Cancer Research (NFCR), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Center for Media Initiatives--dist. learn., 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Centers--Peking Yale
    - Peking/ Yale, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - RC Levin, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Chemical Biology, 1998 April 25 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - CESOF, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Classroom Study, 2001 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Combustion Center, 2000 August 10 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - COI
    - 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Minutes, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Policies, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - GAO, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - GAO Site Visit, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Committees, 2000 June 26 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - CT Ag Experiment Stn, 2001 November 30 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - CT CII, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - CT Tech Council, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - CCR
    - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Cooperative Research
    - Budget, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Equality in New Ventures, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Licensing, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Medical, 2001 July 30 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Patent/ Policy, 2001 December 4 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Office of Cooperative Research
      - General, 2001 February 19 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Personnel, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Review Meeting, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Royalty Sharing, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Corporate Partners Program, 2000- 2001 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Courses (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Course Stats
  - Cure, 2001 August 23 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - DSSG, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Development
    - Development, 2001 August 3 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Corporate Relations, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Corp Relations--Microsoft, 2001 November 6 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Corp Relations--IBM, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Corp Relations--Exxon Mobil, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Equipment, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Educational Alliance
    - 2001 Nov 7 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Bristol Myers Squibb (BMS), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Endowment
    - Mathematics, 2001 February 15 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Physics, 2001 December 11 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Psychology, 2001 July 11 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Engineering
    - Administration, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Fleury, 2001 April 11 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Bldg./Long-Range Planning/Space, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Long-Range Space Planning Comm., 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Background/Policies/ Planning, 1980-1999 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Bromley, D.A., 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Bromley/ V. Bush Award, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Environment
    - ACEM, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Miscellaneous, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - ESC Steering Committee, 2001 December 5 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Environmental Studies, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Environ Sci Fac (ESF)
    - Budget, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Design Team Meeting, 2001 March 29 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Equipment Transfer, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Faculty Affairs (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Faculty Orientation, 2000-2001
  - Faculty Search Procedures, 2000 November 20 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - FAS Nonladder, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Fellowships
    - Environ Engineering, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Packard, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - G and G Computing, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Grants and Contracts
    - Admin Budget, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - General, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Survey, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Gift Stewardship Committee
    - GS Committee, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - GS Fellowships, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Gifts
    - Gifts, 2001 January 3 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Gift Assessment, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Gifts vs. Grants, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Graduate School
    - Admissions, 2001 May 15 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Contingency Plan, 2001 November 29 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Fellowship Opportunity, 2001 September 25 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Fellowships, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Pfizer, 2000 October 18 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Teaching Fellows, 1997-2001 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Teaching Fellow Allocations, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Haskins
    - Renovations, 2000 February 28 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Hellman Family Fellowship
    - 2001 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 2000 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - History of Science, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - HHMI
    - Professors, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Misc., 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Human Resources
    - Misc., 1999 November 11 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Personnel, 2001 August 6 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Wages, 2001 September 21 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Staff Job Audits, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Interdisciplinary Dept., 2000 February 8 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - ITS
    - Budget, 2000 October 24 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Committees- ITSAC, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - FAS ACAD Computing, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Info Sec, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Network Charges, 2001 June 17 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Science Departments, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Leaves of Absence, 2001 November 5 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Library- Kline Science, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Marsh Garden, 2000 February 8 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Math Slots, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Mortgage Assistance, 2001 January 2 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Moving Expenses, 1998 August 3 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - MRSEC, 2001 September 10 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - NE-CAT, 2001 January 25 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Next Economy Partners, 2001 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - OCR
  - OEHS, 2000 October 31 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Oracle, 2001 November 28 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Outside Positions, 2001 December 27 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Peabody Museum
    - General, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Budget, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Grants, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - ESF Collaboration Move, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Master Plan, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Ornithology, 2001 December 13 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Personnel, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Peking Yale Center, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - PI Handbook, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Postdocs
    - General, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Association, 2001 July 16 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Benefits, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Geso, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Other Universities, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Survey, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Prizes and Awards (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Proposals, 2000-2001
    - Astronomy, 2001 August 14 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - Beckman, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - General, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - Dryfus
      - 2001 (Box 5, Folder 169)
      - 2000 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - Equipment, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Intel, 1997 June 13 (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - Johnson and Johnson, 2000 February 22 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - NSF/MRI, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 176 - 177)
    - NSF/ MRSEC, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - MRSEC, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Packard, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - Welch, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - Whitaker, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 182 - 183)
    - Woodrow Wilson, 2001 August 23 (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Provost
    - Committees, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 185 - 187)
    - Hohenberg, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Meetings, 2001 November 5 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - Senior Admin Assoc. (Sciand Tech), 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - Office, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - Other Universities--Duke, 2001 February 27 (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - Retreats, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - PSAC, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Public Affairs, 2000 January 19 (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Rankings
    - AAU, 2001 October 11 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Other, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 197)
  - Recommendation Letters, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - Regional Center, 2000 November 20 (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - Retirement
    - 2000 (Box 5, Folder 200 - 201)